Today, let's take a look at how to quickly process the belt date buckle.
You can see that the belt has been simulated to have this effect.
You need to insert a date buckle.
You can insert the date buckle component prepared in advance into the 3D window.
Drag it to the 3D window, select the load type, select open.
Select the component of the object, click OK.
After adding it, turn off the date buckle window.
Now, use the glue tool to stick the component to the plate first.
Adjust the position of the component.
Insert it into this plate.
Now click empty simulation.
After simulation, you can see that the plate and the component will fall down.
Pause the simulation to cancel.
Because the component has a weight, select the component in the object window.
Find the weight under the property editor.
You can adjust it to 0.1.
After adjustment, select the two plates of the belt.
Right-click to harden.
Convenient simulation.
After hardening, now you need to adjust the position on the other side.
Adjusting the effect of clinging together.
Now the duplicate simulation will fall down.
You can select this plate.
Right-click to freeze.
Another plate.
You can add a fixed pin.
Press the W key to click the plate.
After adding.
Now click empty simulation.
Select the fixed pin.
Move the mouse.
Move the plate to the place where it needs to be glued together.
Eat the surface like this.
Move to the overlap position.
After moving up, you can see the location of the duplicate.
It's down there.
And select the case to rotate it.
This makes it easier to move the palette to the inside of the case.
When we're done,
Bye.
Normally you can click blank simulation.
After simulation, you can see the plate will deform a bit.
Because now it has a conflict in the secondary key
Select secondary key
In the property editor, you can see that it has a conflict
Now pause the simulation
Conflict is equivalent to the secondary key has a safe distance
Can participate in the simulation
You can select the secondary key right key
After the right key
You can see that there are three options in the secondary key simulation
Freeze activation and reverse activation
You can do reverse activation
Reverse activation is equivalent to this secondary key in the 3D window
Not involved in the simulation
Now click on the control block to simulate
The board can pass through this secondary key at will
Press the W key to click on the board
Add a fixed pin
Adjust to the position of the third hole
Then click on the control block to simulate on this side
Pull it over
Tighten it a little
Rotate the angle
Move down
Here come down a little bit
After adjustment, select this board
Move this belt plate board out
Click on the simulation
Let it simulate inside the belt plate
Press the W key to click on the fixed pin
Can delete this fixed pin
After adjustment
Now come to this place where the secondary key just came
Slightly adjust again
Adjusted
Now adjust this one
Add a fixed pin simulation
followed by
After adjustment
Now you can select the secondary key
Right-click to activate
Then the freezing panel
Select it now
It can also activate the panel
Now the negatives are not needed
Press the W key
Click on the縁 acceptance
Reset
You can select the date button of the object window in the property editor to change it to a type
Change to metal
Now click on the control key to simulate
After simulation, you can see that now the component and this version
Have the effect of a real window
Because now the component simulation is conflicted
You can see that when we move the board
The component can be simulated in the hole of the window ring
Will not wear
Now select the board and click on the disarm
The above is the method of wearing the date button
Thank you for watching